putlocker-downloader.net 2013-10-20

# PutLockerDownloader.com - Privacy Policy

We respect your right to privacy. Any details that you give to us via this website or in any other way may be added to our database. You do not have to give us any personal information in order to use most of this website or our software, however, if you wish to take advantage of some of the personalized services that we may from time to time offer, you will need to provide this information.

Your Consent:

By using our website you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in the manner set out in this privacy policy. If we change or modify this privacy policy we shall post these changes on this page.

Use of Personal Details:

Our database of personal details (however we collect these details) is used by us, and third parties acting on our behalf, for administration and marketing related purposes. We may, from time to time, send you mailings which you have requested or we feel may interest you and/or are relevant to you. Such mailings may include details of our products and services e.g. newsletters and other related matters.

Contacting us About Your Information:

If you would like to see the information we hold about you or would like to be removed from our database and/or any mailing lists, or require another form of assistance, please contact support at: [info@coolmirage.com](mailto:info@coolmirage.com)

Cookies:

We may use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data which is stored on your computer's hard drive which makes it easier to identify you and which is revealed to us when you use this website. We also use cookies to track the interest of our users so that we can subsequently enhance their experience on our website. You can configure your web browser not to accept cookies, although this may affect how you see and are able to use this website.

Search Providers and Other Policies:
